# HAIQING (CONNIE) KANG

33-29 163rd St, Flushing, NY | 814-441-6329 | hqk1121@gmail.com

### **OBJECTIVE**

Accomplished healthcare data analyst and self-taught software developer with a passion for developing scalable web applications and working across the full stack. Hoping to combine excellent problem-solving skills and technical knowledges to provide an exciting and easy-to-use app experience for users.

### **EDUCATION**

Flatiron School, New York, NY

Computer Software Engineering Dec 2021

New York University, New York, NY

Master of Arts in Quantitative Economics and Econometrics May 2018

GPA: 3.76/4.00

The Pennsylvania State University, University Park, PA

May 2016 Bachelor of Arts in Economics

Major GPA: 3.90/4.00; Cumulative GPA: 3.62/4.00

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Fidelis Care, New York, NY

Manager, Value-Based Payment Initiatives Data Analytics

September 2020 – August 2021

- Managed the database for over 50 VBP partners, who oversee more than 34,000 providers and manage the care of over 900,000 Medicaid lives, with the goals to reduce cost and improve overall quality of care
- Collaborate cross-functionally with IT team and third-party analytics vendors to provide project requirements, resolve data issue, identify opportunities for report automation and database improvement
- Identified and developed meaningful data strategies through effective communication with stakeholders
- Spearheaded a team of 4 data analysts to effectively manage the data need for 53 VBP partners

#### Chinese Community Accountable Care Organization, New York, NY

Team Lead, Data Analyst

Graduate Research Assistant

July 2018 – September 2020

- Cleaned, compiled, and analyzed large claim data using Microsoft SQL Server, Python and Microsoft Excel
- Developed and maintained physician-facing population health dashboard from multiple data sources using Power BI to help practices better understand their patients
- Worked closely with more than 300 physicians on multiple healthcare initiatives and data reporting

## New York University – Leonard N. Stern School of Business, New York, NY

February 2017 – June 2017

- Compiled, prioritized, sorted, and processed companies' information into local database
- Utilized STATA and Microsoft Excel to track, clean, merge and analyze data in order to study companies' strategies
- Researched and gathered company information using Bloomberg terminal and maintained accurate records

### **PROJECT**

### Empire Health Website/Portal, 2019

Environment: Express.js, Node.js, MangoDB, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Semantic UI, Heroku

- Independently developed a webapp to improve company's public presence, educate members on company highlights, and facilitate event registrations for members
- Collaborate with a third-party developer team to embed a HIPPA-compliant provider portal, which allows members to log in and view the population health dashboard that we built

#### **SKILLS**

- Web Technologies & Frameworks: Express.js, HTML, CSS, PHP, Django
- Scripts/UI: JavaScript, Python, JQuery, BootStrap, Semantic UI, JAVA
- Database and ORM: MySQL, Microsoft SQL server, PostgreSQL